

Ali Bami

Web Developer, Web Designer

About Me

Junior Web Developer with approximately 1 year of practical experience and 2 years of web development school, I'm seeking to obtain a creative and challenging position that utilizes my current knowledge of web development and design. I have a positive attitude and I am always eager to learn new skills. I am comfortable working both independently and as part of a team.

Professional Experience

Web Development consultant at DevPort Gothenburg (june 2023-current)

Working as a Junior Web Developer and participating in coding, testing, debugging new applications and website with the team of designers, developers, and content creators to create digital

Freelance Web Developer **Gothenburg (maj 2023-current)**

I am currently working on a hotel website using Next.js. In this project, I am also implementing a backend system to interact with customer data

Team Manager Backup at Svenska Spel, Gothenburg (2018-current)

As a team manager, I oversee work, support staff, communicate with clients and colleagues, participate in meetings, handle orders, budgets, and expenses. I manage and set product prices, liaise with Trivec support for system-related matters, and utilize Domino for invoicing, daily reports, and account reconciliation.

Web Developer Intern at Wallmander Co., **Gothenburg (2023-maj 2023)**

I created an WebSIte that fetched flight data from an API and displayed it. I connected the database to our application and presented the data within it. Additionally, I designed and deployed the website from scratch using MongoDB, Tailwind CSS, and Next.js.

Web Developer Intern at Triple Down, Stockholm (2022)

I have worked with an automated PRIIPs software, designed to simplify compliance processes, improve customer experience, and generate PRIIPs documents.

Waiter/Bartender BigBar, Part-time Forli (2014-2016)

My Contact

ali.bami@medieinstitutet.se

0765876515



Gothenburg, Sweden.



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ali-b-374813135

Skills

JavaScript, React.js, Next.js, HTML, CSS, MaterialUI, Node.js, MySQL MongoDB, Sanity, Domino

Education Background

- Webdeveloper with REACT,IT-Högskolan, Gothenburg (2023)
- Full Stack Developer Program at Medieinstitutet, Gothenburg (2021-2023)

Swedish as a second language at

Hermods AB, Gothenburg (2019)

- Master's degree in mass media and politics at Alma Mater Studiorum, Università di Bologna (2016)
- Bachelor's Degree in Political Science -International Relations at Alma Mater Studiorum, Università di Bologna (2014)

Languages

Swedish English Albanian Italian